Railway Labor Executives' Association Records 5484
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series VII: Office Files, 1964
  - Government: NRAB, Second Division, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Government: NRAB Third Division, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 15)
  - Government: NRAB, Fourth Division, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 16)
  - Government: NRAB, Organizations Qualified to Participate in Selection of Members, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 17)
  - Government: NRAB, Membership, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - Government: BLF and E vs. Monon Railroad, National Mediation Board C. 3196, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Government: NRAB, Application of Awards, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - Government: NRAB, Third Party Notices, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 21)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 22)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Data Distributed at RLEA Meetings [folder 1 of 2], 1964 (Box 112, Folder 23a)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Data Distributed at RLEA Meetings [folder 2 of 2], 1964 (Box 112, Folder 23b)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Membership and Staff Appointments, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 24)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Administrative Practice and Procedures, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 25)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Field Offices, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 26)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Mechanizations and Centralizations of Claims' Payments, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 27)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Coverage of Railroads and Unions as Employers, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 28)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Status of Funds, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 29)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Military Service Credits, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 30)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Educational Program, Meetings, Films, Etc., 1964 (Box 112, Folder 31)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Press Releases, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 32)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Supplemental Retirement Plans [folder 1 of 2], 1964 (Box 112, Folder 33a)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Supplemental Retirement Plans [folder 2 of 2], 1964 (Box 112, Folder 33b)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Safety Studies, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 34)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, National Reporting, Officers' Memoranda and Meetings, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 35)
  - Legislation: General (File 1) [folder 1 of 2], 1964 (Box 113, Folder 1a)
  - Legislation: General (File 1)[folder 2 of 2], 1964 (Box 113, Folder 1b)
  - Legislation: General (File 2), 1964 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: Manpower Development and Training Act Amendments [folder 1 of 2], 1964 (Box 113, Folder 3a)
  - Legislation: Manpower Development and Training Act Amendments [folder 2 of 2], 1964 (Box 113, Folder 3b)
  - Legislation: National Capital Transit Agency, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: Time Uniformity Bills, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: A Bold Tax Program for Progress, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Legislation: Civil Rights Fair Employment Practices Commission, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: Railway Labor Act, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Legislation: Interstate Commerce Act, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Legislation: Highway Financing Trust Fund, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - Legislation: Repeal of taxes on transportation of Persons, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Legislation: National Transportation Policy, Inter-Agency Group, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - Legislation: Repeal of Section 13(a) of Interstate Commerce Act, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - Legislation: Minimum Rate Exemptions, Omnibus Bill, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - Legislation: National Railroad Freight Car Supply, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 15)
  - Legislation: Interstate Commerce Act (ICA), Freight Forwarder Bill, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 16)
  - Legislation: Amendment of ICA, S. 1719, State Income Tax Laws [folder 1 of 2], 1964 (Box 113, Folder 17a)
  - Legislation: Amendment of ICA, S. 1719, State Income Tax Laws [folder 2 of 2], 1964 (Box 113, Folder 17b)
  - Legislation: Railroad Retirement Act [folder 1 of 2], 1964 (Box 113, Folder 18a)
  - Legislation: Railroad Retirement Act [folder 2 of 2], 1964 (Box 113, Folder 18b)
  - Legislation: Railroad Retirement Act Amendments (Railroad Retirement Board), 1964 (Box 113, Folder 19)
  - Legislation: Railroad Pension Conference Postcards re: Amending Railroad Retirement Act, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 20)
  - Legislation: Railroad Unemployment Insurance Act, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 21)
  - Legislation: Labor-Management Relations, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 22)
  - Legislation: Social Security Act, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 23)
  - Legislation: Medical Benefits to Retired persons (Medicare), 1964 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Legislation: Mail, Parcel Post, and Express, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: State Legislation [folder 1 of 2], 1964 (Box 114, Folder 3a)
  - Legislation: State Legislation [folder 2 of 2], 1964 (Box 114, Folder 3b)
  - Legislation: Full Crew laws, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: Right-To-Work Laws, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: State Public Utilities Commissions, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Legislation: Coal Slurry Pipeline Legislation, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act, Also Welfare and Pension Plans Disclosure Act, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Legislation: National Labor Relations Act, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Legislation: American Municipal Association, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Legislation: Mass Transit, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Legislation: Bills Pertaining to Federal Employees and veterans, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Legislation: Waterways, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - Legislation: Anti-Labor Legislation, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - Legislation: Depressed Areas, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - Legislation: Minimum Wage Legislation, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - Legislation: Hours of Service Law Amendments, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 17)
  - Legislation: Clayton Act Amendments, Rail merger Moratorium, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 18)
  - Legislation: Congressional Investigation of Railroad Finances, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 19)
  - Legislation: Conservation Legislation, Interior Department, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 20)
  - Legislation: Settlement of Railroad Work Rules Dispute (S. J. Res.182), 1964 (Box 114, Folder 21)
  - Legislation: Hart Subcommittee Hearings on Economic Concentration, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 22)
  - Legislation: Railroad Safety Legislation, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 23)
  - Government: House and Senate, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 24)
  - Government: Constitution, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 25)
  - Government: Executive Branch, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 26)
  - Government: Congressional Campaign Contribution requests, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 27)
  - Government: State Department, General, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 28)
  - Government: State Department, John K. Meskimen, A.I.D., 1964 (Box 114, Folder 29)
  - Government: US National Commission in the Pan American Railway Congress, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 30)
  - Government: Treasury Department, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 31)
  - Government: Payroll Savings Division, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 32)
  - Government: Internal Revenue Service, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 33)
  - Government: Defense Department, general, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 34)
  - Government: Office of Emergency Planning (OCDM), 1964 (Box 114, Folder 35)
  - Government: Labor-Management Manpower Policy Committee, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 36)
  - Government: Labor-Management Manpower Policy Committee [folder 1 of 2], 1964 (Box 114, Folder 37a)
  - Government: Labor-Management Manpower Policy Committee [folder 2 of 2], 1964 (Box 114, Folder 37b)
  - Government: Regional Manpower Committee, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 38)
  - Government: National Defense Executive Reserve, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 39)
  - Government: Supplementary Material, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 40)
  - Government: Massachusetts, Civil Defense Agency, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 41)
  - Government: Commerce Department, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 42)
  - Government: Labor Department, General, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 43)
  - Government: Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS), 1963 (Box 114, Folder 44)
  - Government: BLS Wage Chronology #40, Non-Operating Employees, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 45)
  - Government: Bureau of Labor Standards, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 46)
  - Government: Bureau of Labor-Management Reports, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 47)
  - Government: Interstate Commerce Commission, General, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 48)
  - Government: ICC Membership and Staff Appointments, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 49)
  - Government: ICC Rules of Practice and Administrative Procedure, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 50)
  - Government: ICC Statistics, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 51)
  - Government: Proposed New Classification of Class I and II Railroads, Docket No. 34477, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 52)
  - RLEA: AFL-CIO, Speakers' Bureau, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - RLEA: Constitution and By-Laws, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - RLEA: Officers and Members, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - RLEA: American Railway Supervisors Association, 1963-1964 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - RLEA: American Train Dispatchers' Association, 1963-1964 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - RLEA: Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1963-1964 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Government: President's Committee on the Physically Handicapped, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - RLEA: Annual Meetings, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Government: Civil Aeronautics Board, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Government: President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Government: Peace Corps, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Government: President's Commission on the Status of Women, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - Government: Freedom from Hunger Foundation, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - Judicial: Court Cases, General [folder 1 of 2], 1964 (Box 115, Folder 14a)
  - Judicial: Court Cases, General [folder 2 of 2], 1964 (Box 115, Folder 14b)
  - Judicial: Court Cases, Supreme Court Decisions [folder 1 of 2], 1964 (Box 115, Folder 15a)
  - Judicial: Court Cases, Supreme Court Decisions [folder 2 of 2], 1964 (Box 115, Folder 15b)
  - Judicial: Union Shop Case (Looper), 1964 (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - Judicial: Clinchfield Case, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - Judicial: System Fed. No. 91, Red vs. O. V. Wright (Union Shop), 1964 (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - Judicial: L and N, Union Shop, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 19)
  - Judicial: BRT vs. Long Island Rail Road (Strike Insurance), 1964 (Box 115, Folder 20)
  - Judicial: Flight Engineers' Case, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 21)
  - Judicial: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees vs. USA and ICC. In re merger of Chesapeake and Ohio with Baltimore and Ohio, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 22)
  - Judicial: New Jersey v. New York, Susquehanna and Western, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 23)
  - Judicial: Monona Railroad vs. BRT, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 24)
  - RLEA: General, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 25)
  - RLEA: Emergency Relief Fund, Including Kefauver Memorial Fund and Eugene V. Debs Foundation, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 26)
  - RLEA: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 27)
  - RLEA: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 28)
  - RLEA: Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 29)
  - RLEA: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 30)
  - RLEA: Brotherhood of Railway Clerks, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 31)
  - RLEA: Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 32)
  - RLEA: Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 33)
  - RLEA: International Association of Machinists, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 34)
  - RLEA: International Brotherhood of Boilermakers and Blacksmiths, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 35)
  - RLEA: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 36)
  - RLEA: International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 37)
  - RLEA: International Organizations Masters, Mates, and Pilots of America, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 38)
  - RLEA: National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 39)
  - RLEA: Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 40)
  - RLEA: Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 41)
  - RLEA: Railway Employees Department, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 42)
  - RLEA: Sheet Metal Workers' International Association, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 43)
  - RLEA: Switchmen's Union of North America, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 44)
  - RLEA: Seafarers' International Union of North America, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 45)
  - RLEA: Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 46)
  - RLEA: Canadian Affairs, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 47)
  - RLEA: Meetings, General, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 48)
  - RLEA: 1964 Miami Beach Meeting (Box 115, Folder 49)
  - RLEA: Agendas, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 50)
  - RLEA: Reports of Counsel, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 51)
  - RLEA: Assessments, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 52)
  - RLEA: Applications for Affiliation, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 53)
  - RLEA: Emergency Boards [folder 1 of 3], 1964 (Box 115, Folder 54a)
  - RLEA: Emergency Boards [folder 2 of 3], 1964 (Box 115, Folder 54b)
  - RLEA: Emergency Boards [folder 3 of 3], 1964 (Box 115, Folder 54c)
  - RLEA: Brotherhood Railway Carmen of America, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 55)
  - RLEA: Southern Rules Movement, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - RLEA: Chicago and North Western Rules Movement, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - RLEA: Butte, Anaconda and Pacific Rules Movement, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - RLEA: Job Stabilization Movement on the MKT Railroad, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - RLEA: 1961 Rules Movement (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - RLEA: Radio-Telephone Equipment (FCC), 1964 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - RLEA: 1962 Rules Movement, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - RLEA: CIM Railway, Section 6 Notice, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - RLEA: Florida East Coast Railway, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - RLEA: L and N Railroad "No Injury" Report Forms, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - RLEA: 1963 Rules Movement [folder 1 of 2], 1964 (Box 116, Folder 11a)
  - RLEA: 1963 Rules Movement [folder 2 of 2], 1964 (Box 116, Folder 11b)
  - RLEA: Emergency Boards 161,162,163, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - RLEA: Changes in Discipline Policy and Procedures, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - RLEA: Employment and Medical Examination Policy and Procedures, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - RLEA: N and W Railway, "Thrift Plan" for Non-Union Employees, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - RLEA: Travelers Insurance Company, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - RLEA: Health and Welfare, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - RLEA: Operating Unions [folder 1 of 2], 1964 (Box 116, Folder 18a)
  - RLEA: Operating Unions [folder 2 of 2], 1964 (Box 116, Folder 18b)
  - RLEA: Automation, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 19)
  - RLEA: Rules Committee, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 20)
  - RLEA: Carrier Strike Insurance Program, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 21)
  - RLEA: Union Shop, General, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 22)
  - RLEA: Union Dues, General, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 23)
  - RLEA: Diversification of Railroad (Piggyback), 1964 (Box 116, Folder 24)
  - RLEA: Permits on Railroad Property for Union Business, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 25)
  - RLEA: Railway Labor Building, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 26)
  - RLEA: Committees, General, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 27)
  - RLEA: Safety Committee, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 28)
  - RLEA: Public Relations Committee, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 29)
    Includes PA RR - NYC PR Program
  - RLEA: Committee to Study Railroad Mergers, Etc., 1964 (Box 116, Folder 30)
  - RLEA: Safety Legislation, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 31)
  - RLEA: "The Railroad Industry: A Critical Examination and Appraisal of the Merger Dilemma", 1964 (Box 116, Folder 32)
    By L. Keyserling
  - RLEA: Legislative Representatives, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 33)
  - RLEA: Passes, General, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 34)
  - RLEA: Personnel Records, General, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 35)
  - RLEA: Prospective Employees, General, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 36)
  - RLEA: Finances, General, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 37)
  - RLEA: Financial Statements, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 38)
  - RLEA: Workmen's Compensation Tax, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 39)
  - RLEA: Travelers Insurance Company, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 40)
  - RLEA: GPO, Account No. 11256, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 41)
  - RLEA: Insurance, General, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 42)
  - RLEA: Addressograph, Multigraph Corporation, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 43)
  - RLEA: Postage meter, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 44)
  - RLEA: Office Equipment, General, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 45)
  - RLEA: The Thermo-Fax Copy Machine, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 46)
  - RLEA: Office Furniture, General, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 47)
  - RLEA: Registration for Lobbying, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 48)
  - RLEA: Lawyers Bills, General [folder 1 of 3], 1964 (Box 116, Folder 49a)
  - RLEA: Lawyers Bills, General [folder 2 of 3], 1964 (Box 116, Folder 49b)
  - RLEA: Lawyers Bills, General [folder 3 of 3], 1964 (Box 116, Folder 49c)
  - RLEA: Strikes, General, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 50)
  - RLEA: Florida East Coast Railway Strike [folder 1 of 3], 1964 (Box 117, Folder 1a)
  - RLEA: Florida East Coast Railway Strike [folder 2 of 3], 1964 (Box 117, Folder 1b)
  - RLEA: Florida East Coast Railway Strike [folder 3 of 3], 1964 (Box 117, Folder 1c)
  - RLEA: Florida East Coast Railway Company v. RLEA [folder 1 of 3], 1964 (Box 117, Folder 2a)
  - RLEA: Florida East Coast Railway Company v. RLEA [folder 2 of 3], 1964 (Box 117, Folder 2b)
  - RLEA: Florida East Coast Railway Company v. RLEA [folder 3 of 3], 1964 (Box 117, Folder 2c)
  - Railroads: General, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Railroads: Illinois Central Industries, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Railroads: Baltimore Port Authority, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Railroads: Commonwealth, Edison-NYC Coal Conveyor, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Railroads: B and O, Control and Operation of Reading Company, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Railroads: Association of American Railroads, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Railroads: AAR, Highway user Charges [folder 1 of 2], 1964 (Box 117, Folder 9a)
  - Railroads: AAR, Highway user Charges [folder 2 of 2], 1964 (Box 117, Folder 9b)
  - Railroads: Transport Statistics, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Railroads: Association of Western Railways, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Railroads: Carriers' Conference Committees, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Railroads: National Railway Labor Conference, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Railroads: Hospital Associations, general, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Railroads: Kansas City Southern, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Railroads: Missouri Pacific, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Railroads: Illinois Central, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - Railroads: Southern Pacific Hospital Association, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - Railroads: Western Pacific Hospital Association, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - Other Organizations: Miscellaneous Organizations [folder 1 of 2], 1964 (Box 117, Folder 20a)
  - Other Organizations: Miscellaneous Organizations [folder 2 of 2], 1964 (Box 117, Folder 20b)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO, Miscellaneous Organizations, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Other Organizations: Collective Bargaining Reports, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 22)
  - Other Organizations: Free Trade Union News, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 23)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO Minutes, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 24)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO Legislative Action Bulletin, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 25)
  - Other Organizations: Legislative Council, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 26)
  - Other Organizations: Union Materials, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 27)
  - Other Organizations: Advertising Council, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 28)
  - Other Organizations: National Safety Council, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 29)
  - Other Organizations: Pension Associations, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Other Organizations: Young Men's Christian Association, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Other Organizations: Harvard University, Trade Union Program, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 3a)
  - Other Organizations: Committee for National Trade Policy, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 3b)
  - Other Organizations: the Unions Retirement Foundation, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Other Organizations: Nat'l Conference on Int'l Economic and Social Development, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Other Organizations: US Committee for the United Nations [folder 1 of 2], 1964 (Box 118, Folder 6a)
  - Other Organizations: US Committee for the United Nations [folder 2 of 2], 1964 (Box 118, Folder 6b)
  - Other Organizations: Research Institute of America recommendations, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Other Organizations: Transportation Research Forum, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Other Organizations: American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Other Organizations: Charities, General, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Other Organizations: American Cancer Society, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Other Organizations: National Association of Retired and Veteran Railway Employees, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Other Organizations: Dual Organizations ("Paper", "Rump"), 1964 (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Other Organizations: Labor Bureau of Middle West, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - Other Organizations: LABOR Newspaper, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Other Organizations: Special Edition of LABOR for KEATING, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Other Organizations: Special Election Year Editions of LABOR, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - International Affairs: General [folder 1 of 2], 1964 (Box 118, Folder 18a)
  - International Affairs: General [folder 2 of 2], 1964 (Box 118, Folder 18b)
  - International Affairs: Japanese Exchange Program [folder 1 of 2], 1964 (Box 118, Folder 19a)
  - International Affairs: Japanese Exchange Program [folder 2 of 2], 1964 (Box 118, Folder 19b)
  - International Affairs: Supplementary Material Re: Japanese Exchange Program, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 20)
  - International Affairs: Swedish Railway Union, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 21)
  - International Affairs: Office of International Labor Affairs, 1st Half [folder 1 of 2] [folder 1 of 4], 1964 (Box 118, Folder 22a)
  - International Affairs: Office of International Labor Affairs, 1st Half [folder 1 of 2] [folder 2 of 4], 1964 (Box 118, Folder 22b)
  - International Affairs: Office of International Labor Affairs, 1st Half [folder 1 of 2] [folder 3 of 4], 1964 (Box 118, Folder 22c)
  - International Affairs: OILA, Team Managers, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 23)
  - International Affairs: Trade Union Advisory Committee, Labor Department, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - International Affairs: Joint US-Mexican Trade Union Committee, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 25)
  - International Affairs: International Labor Office, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 26)
  - International Affairs: News form the ILO, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 27)
  - International Affairs: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 28)
  - International Affairs: ICFTU, Press Releases, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 29)
  - International Affairs: ICFTU, News Releases, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 30)
  - International Affairs: ICFTU, Radio Service, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 31)
  - International Affairs: ICFTU, Spotlight, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 32)
  - International Affairs: ICFTU, Press Communique, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 33)
  - International Affairs: ICFTU, Information Bulletin, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 34)
  - International Affairs: ICFTU, Constitution, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 35)
  - Commuter Problems: High Speed Rail, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 36)
  - Commuter Problems: General, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 37)
  - Commuter Problems: New Haven Problem Including New York Area [folder 1 of 2], 1964 (Box 118, Folder 38a)
  - Commuter Problems: New Haven Problem Including New York Area [folder 2 of 2], 1964 (Box 118, Folder 38b)
  - Commuter Problems: New England Railroad Study, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 39)